nzcity.co.nz 2019-02-26

# New Zealand City - Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement New Zealand City Ltd (NZCity)

New Zealand City Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this and the following listed Web sites: **[nzcity.co.nz](https://www.nzcity.co.nz/), [www.searchnz.co.nz](http://www.searchnz.co.nz/), [www.rugbyleague.co.nz](http://www.rugbyleague.co.nz/), [www.crime.co.nz](http://www.crime.co.nz/)**

Please note this statement is as at 30 Jun 1999. NZCity is always evolving and will endeavour to remain within the bounds of this statement or keep this statement current. NZCity will always endeavour to comply with the conditions of the New Zealand Privacy Act. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help gather broad demographic information that is not tied back to you personally.

Our site uses cookies to to deliver content specific to your interests and store your personalisation options.

Our site's personalisation form is optional but asks users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), and may ask for demographic information (like age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the personalisation form to send the user information about our company if the "allow mail out option" is ticked. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor if absolutely necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by simply changing the mail out option, by the special link on the mailing or by methods described below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

This site contains links to other sites. **NZCity** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Parts of our site may use an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, and provide information about our company, The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

From time to time we may run optional online surveys in which we may ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We may run promotions on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We may use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary usually for prize delivery. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company and should be treated as an external site. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We maintain a secure private network for storage of your personal information. 

## Children's Guidelines

We recommend children are supervised online with parental guidence. In particular our chat, forums, message boards or news groups give children an outlet where they may provide personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from NZCity.

NZCity gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can visit the following URL: https://home.nzcity.co.nz/personalise/
  2. Or visit Our contact form and give us enough detail to correct the problem. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. visit https://home.nzcity.co.nz/personalise/ to personalise this web site 
  2. visit Our contact form and give us enough detail to correct the problem. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Webmaster New Zealand City Ltd P.O.Box 30772 Lower Hutt New Zealand Our contact form   
_Please note: we do not provide email addresses to prevent spamming engines collecting them  
If you need an email address please use webmaster at nzcity.co.nz, replacing the at and spaces with the @ sign. __  
_
